export default {
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question" : "Which matches the start of a string?",
      "options": [
        "^",
        "$",
        "?"
      ],
      "answer": "^"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question" : "Which matches the end of a string?",
      "options": [
        "^",
        "$",
        "?"
      ],
      "answer": "^"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question" : "What is the output of \"abcd\"[2:]",
      "options": [
        "a",
        "ab",
        "cd"
      ],
      "answer": "cd"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question" : "What is the output of ab{3}c?",
      "options": [
        "abc",
        "abbbc",
        "abbbbc"
      ],
      "answer": "abbbc"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question" : "What is the output of [(AB)(B\\\\d)\\\\2\\\\1]?",
      "options": [
        "ABB2B2AB",
        "ABBAB",
        "ABB2B2"
      ],
      "answer": "ABB2B2AB"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question" : "The 'NO-CACHE' cache-control response header prohibits documents from being stored on the client.",
      "options": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "answer": "false"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question" : "Which is the most commonly used session hijacking attack?",
      "options": [
        "IP hacking",
        "IP spooling",
        "IP spoofing",
        "IP tracking"
      ],
      "answer": "IP spoofing"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question" : "Which of them is an example of grabbing email information?",
      "options": [
        "Cookie stealing",
        "Reverse engineering",
        "Port scanning",
        "Banner grabbing"
      ],
      "answer": "Cookie stealing"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question" : "Which of the following is not a strong security protocol?",
      "options": [
        "HTTPS",
        "SSL",
        "SMTP",
        "SFTP"
      ],
      "answer": "SMTP"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question" : "VPNs use encryption techniques to maintain security and privacy which communicating remotely via public network.",
      "options": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "answer": "true"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question" : "Which of these is an example of a possible victim of a phishing attack?",
      "options": [
        "The website that was hacked ",
        "The person who had their identity stolen",
        "The bank of the victim",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": "All of these"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question" : "Secure cookies have which feature?",
      "options": [
        "They are not encrypted, just sent via secure server",
        "They are encrypted",
        "Secure cookies are passed along via encrypted programs",
        "Cookies are always traded between trusted users"
      ],
      "answer": "They are encrypted"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question" : "What does cross-site scripting allow for attackers?",
      "options": [
        "Direct introduction of viruses into a victim's computer",
        "The introduction of worm viruses into the victims website",
        "Injection of client side scripts into web pages"
      ],
      "answer": "Injection of client side scripts into web pages"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question" : "What is one way that a web browser is vulnerable to breaching?",
      "options": [
        "A browser can be infected by closing it",
        "A virus can be sent through the monitor",
        "A browser plugin can be exploited",
        "Web browsers are impervious to exploitation"
      ],
      "answer": "A browser plugin can be exploited"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question" : "Which of the following are possible security threats?",
      "options": [
        "Illegitimate use",
        "Backdoors",
        "Masquerading",
        "All of the given options are correct"
      ],
      "answer": "All of the given options are correct"
    }
  ]
}